freetubetv.net 2012-09-30

# FreeTube Privacy Policy

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at _support@freetube.uni.cc_. 

At FreeTube, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected by FreeTube and how it is used. 

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, FreeTube makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
FreeTube uses cookies to store information about visitors preferences, channel selections, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser or components.

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site to further track users consumptive patterns across our site, as well as other third party sites utilizing their services.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to display advertisements and links that appear on FreeTube. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

We utilize the [DoubleClick cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx) to help advertisers and publishers manage and serve ads on FreeTube and other Google adsense powered sites. Advertisers may serve ads based on interests associated with non-personally identifiable online activity, such as videos viewed, frequency of uploading or activity on other AdSense partner sites. Advertisers may also serve ads to you based on previous activity on that advertiser's website. This non-personally identifiable information is held separately from your FreeTube Account data, or other personally identifying information in our possession.

You may at any time view, add, edit to the interest categories used to provide you with relevant advertisements by using the [Ads Preference Manager](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences?hl=en-US) for the DoubleClick cookie. Your preferences will be adjusted and respected across FreeTube, and all other Google Adsense DoubleClick affiliated sites. For more information regarding interest-based advertising, pleasee see the Ad Preference Manager [FAQ](http://www.google.com/privacy_faq.html).

You may also may choose to [opt out of the DoubleClick cookie](http://optout.doubleclick.com/cgi-bin/optoutgoogle.pl) at any time. If you opt-out, ads delivered to your browser by our ad-serving technology will not be served based on the DoubleClick cookie. Find more information [here](http://www.google.com/privacy_faq.html) about opting out of the DoubleClick cookie. 

FreeTube does not provide or disclose any personal information to third-party companies or ad-servers, without your consent. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. FreeTube's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.
